Hanna Gaudasińska-Zapaśnik

Web developer



Personal information

Location: Warsaw

Phone: +48 506 042 937

E-mail: hgz.devi@gmail.com

WWW: https://hgzdev.github.io/cv

GitHub: https://github.com/HGZdev

Languages

Polish: Native

English: Advanced

Additional skills

Graphics software:

COREL Photo-Paint, Photoshop

Statistical software:

SPSS, STATA, SAS Base, Atlas.ti

MS Office:

Excel (VBA), PowerPoint, Word

Hobbies

Historical linguistics, archeology and handicraft

I am a software programmer with 3-years' professional experience, specializing in website development. My field of expertise ranges from front-end to 'soft' back-end technologies. During my career I was involved in user-interfaces creation as well as client-server communication, databases architecture design and testing. Moreover, my experience gained in the previous profession of a market researcher allows me to successfully play the role of a client liaison in the field of technological analysis of requirements, functionalities implementation and training. I am looking for job opportunities that will allow me to utilize my potential and broaden my skills and knowledge comprehensively, under the guidance of experienced mentors. I kindly invite you to look at my GitHub portfolio.

Key skills



Work experience

10.2017 - Yaska Polska Sp. z o.o.

Web developer

- Website development for Belgian companies and non-profit organizations
- Modern user-interfaces creation (React.js, Final-form, styled-components and more)
- Co-design of the apps architecture based on the StratoKit/strato-db engine (SQlite, GraphQL, Node.js, Redux-like events flow)
- Unit-, integration- and end-to-end testing (Jest, Cypress.js)
- Client liaison: recognition of the needs and their technological implementation

12.2016 -	VoiceMap - GPS audioguides
02.2017	Preparation of an audioguide tour around Krakowskie Przedmieście St. in Warsaw
05.2013 -	TNS Polska S.A. – Automotive Department
05.2015	Junior Research Executive
	- Propagation and coordination of augustitative mustary changing and customers

- Preparation and coordination of quantitative, mystery shopping and customer satisfaction surveys for leading automotive and oil companies
- Coordination of TNS Garage Quality Check countrywide survey
- 09.2012 ACNielsen Polska Sp. z o.o. Manufacturer Client Service
 03.2013 Marketing Research Consulting Programme
 06.2010 L'Oreal Polska Sp. z o.o. Media and Market Research Division

Workshops & trainings

internship

09.2017 -	Conference Google Developer Days in Kraków Participation in workshops on Progressive Web Design, Firebase and Google Maps
04.2017 - 06.2017	Coders Lab – bootcamp: "Become Front-End Developer" Intensive training for Front-end developer (240h)
02.2016 - 06.2016	Delfin English School, London, United Kingdom General English Course, level: advanced C1+ (150h)
00.2010	General English Course, level. davanced C1+ (15011)

University of Warsaw - the Faculty of Economic Sciences

Education

09 2005 -

12.2010

07.2003	only croining of wardaw the raconty of Economic ociences
07.2012	Specialization: Business Economics (MA 2012)
09.2007 - 06.2012	University of Warsaw – the Institute of Sociology Specialization: Social and Market Research (MA Certificate of Completion 2012)
01.2010 - 06.2010	University College of Maastricht, Netherlands Student Exchange Erasmus Programme, specialization: Social Science

I hereby consent to the processing of my vital and personal data in so far as this is required under the recruitment campaign, in accordance with the Act of August 29, 1997, on the Protection of Personal Information (JoL no. 133, item 883).